

CONTACTS

TECH SKILLS

- Postman

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Responsibility

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MARIIA KONTSEVA

IUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am open for new job opportunities in IT (HTML/CSS/JavaScript/React/Node.js). I have hands-on experience in following Agile/Scrum methodology when working in a team. Also, I have some troubleshooting and code reviewing skills (helped my teammates during studying process and performed the scrum master and teamlead roles on team projects). I am a fast learner, responsible, and ready for challenging tasks.

PROJECTS

ICE CREAM Scrum Master - Team project -[HTML5, CSS3] EventBooster Team Lead - Team project -[JavaScript]

WebStudio Personal project -[HTML5, CSS3]

Gallery

Food service Personal projects -[JavaScript]

Image finder

Feedback statistics

Image finder

Personal projects - [React] Movies Service

Phonebook

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-2021 Assistant at the Department of Technology

> of inorganic substances, water treatment and general chemical technology in Igor

Sikorsky KPI

May-Dec 2020 Engineer of the Chemical Technology

Faculty in Igor Sikorsky KPI

Senior Inspector of the Dean's Office of 2019-2020

the Chemical Technology Faculty in Igor

Sikorsky KPI

EDUCATION

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

Bachelor's degree 2013 - 2017 Master's degree 2017 - 2018 Phd's degree 2019 - now

Chemical technology and engineering

GoIT 2020-2021

Full Stack Developer

Grade Education Centre (Kyiv) Feb-Jun 2019

Upper Intermediate